Hallelujah!
Happy Easter!
Viewers all over the world,
that is the language everywhere - Happy Easter!
I need to use a language you understand. But today, we are going to talk about that revelation.
For the name Jesus is revelation and the message too is revelation.
Even faith is made known by divine revelation.
And even I'm here today - if you are not looking at me through revelation,
you continue to see T.B. Joshua, that your brother that has white hair here.
You may be seated. Thank you
Hallelujah!
Yes
You are not here to see the man.
You are here by revelation to see a man called Prophet,
not a man called T.B. Joshua.
Hallelujah!
T.B. Joshua is your brother. There is a man you need to know by revelation.
That is divine nature.
Hallelujah!
Ok, let's quickly look at the book of 1 Corinthians 12, the name Jesus.
1 Corinthians 12:3:
"Therefore I want you to know that no one who is speaking by the Spirit of God says,
'Jesus be cursed', and no one can say 'Jesus is Lord', except by the help of the Holy Ghost."
You can say "Jesus." It means you cannot just wake up and say "Jesus" without being led.
Because you hear people say "Jesus" and you say "Jesus" - you are calling your brother at home.
I was watching a game yesterday; I saw a guy named Jesus.
And the referee would say "Jesus, Jesus!" and I would say, "What Jesus?"
On the field. That was yesterday, I saw a guy who was playing football - number 7.
His name is Jesus. I said, "Aha! So this is the name some of our people used to call".
And the man cannot help them.
But the Jesus of Nazareth can be revealed to you by revelation.
You must be led by the Spirit to that Jesus -
not to the name of your brother, but to the name of Jesus of Nazareth.
Hallelujah!
Let's read together again. 1 Corinthians 12:3:
"Therefore I want you to know that no one who is speaking by the Spirit of God says..."
But if you call the name Jesus by the help of the Spirit, you will not call your brother at home.
...no one can say 'Jesus is Lord', except by the Holy Ghost."
That is, Holy Spirit. The name Jesus must be revealed to you.
No one can say "Jesus is Lord" except by the Holy Spirit, by the help of the Holy Spirit.
What does that mean? Your God is not a human being.
Because He came from where? To do what?
Because we say "Happy Easter", what is the meaning of Easter?
What do mean? Whom are we celebrating? Is it your brother or someone you know somewhere?
You know revelation brings conviction. And conviction brings real movement.
When we say real movement, we mean, power steps.
The moment you say, "I am a Christian", you talk of power. You can't separate Christianity from power.
Christianity lies in the heart.
Real movement means power steps - steps with intent, purpose.
Revelation is the realisation of something previously not known.
"Hey, Jesus Christ!" - in the power of the Holy Ghost.
Like we are going to see today. We are going to see Jesus in the power of the Holy Ghost
and it will be revealed to you in the Spirit.
Healing is a relation.
Deliverance is a revelation.
Salvation is a revelation.
He said: "Be healed!" You just see people begin to, "What is happening here?"
Just because I said to you that studying the Bible is good for you,
that does not mean that I can get you to believe that studying the Bible is good for you.
You must get that revelation in order to believe.
That is, I had the revelation that studying the Bible is good for you.
That does not mean that I can get you to believe that studying the Bible is good for you.
You must get that revelation in order to believe.
The challenges we have now is that we are too conditioned into believing
that what we are reading in the Bible is for people in the Bible.
When you remember your weakness, your fault, your pitfall,
you say, "'Son of David, have mercy on me', that is for the blind Bartholomew".
You blind today, when you remember your weakness, pitfall, sin,
you say, "No, that cannot work for me. That is for the man".
We are too conditioned into believing that what God said can happen to others
will not happen to you.
That is just the sense.
What God says can happen to others will not happen to you - that is the condition.
We look at all of our weaknesses, sins, pitfalls, faults and say,
"It is not going to happen to me because of my sin".
Remember the message I gave last Sunday.
Success, greatness is not about your weakness, fault, pitfall.
It is about what Jesus did for us at the cross.
He made us fit for God.
He made us what?
Fit! This is what we are talking about today.
Fitness means, your past is over;
your sin has been forgiven.
If your sin has been forgiven, what follows?
He made you fit for God.
Tell your neighbor, "Happy Easter! Jesus made you fit for God!"
I can´t hear you.
Happy Easter! Jesus made you fit for God!
You are a work of art.
If you want to become God's person, follow His process.
Tell your neighbour, "If you want to become God's person, follow His process".
I can't hear you.
"If you want to become God's person, follow His process."
Again.
That is that. That's like you take a pen.
You just begin to draw.
You put hair, you put hand, you put that - you want to put on the picture of T.B. Joshua.
You know where you have to start from.
You say, This is leg, this is hand.
You are a work of art.
If you want to become God's person, follow His process.
All the way to Calvary He went for me
He went to set me free
For you to be here today and join us to celebrate Easter, God prepared you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neightbour, "God prepared me in advance".
Tell your neighbour again, "For me to be here today, God prepared me in advance
before putting me in the fire of life".
He was there before Daniel in the lion's den. That is why the lions turned to friends.
That is why the fire turned to ice because He was there.
God is trying to build character now so that when you get to the place of destiny,
you will not crash, explode and lose it all.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Are you with me?
Nothing good happens without discipline.
Tell your neighbour.
"Nothing good happens without discipline."
I can't hear you.
Again
"Nothing good happens without discipline."
Again and again.
If you count many things that happened to you, that you are not satisfied,
that you are not happy with, you will know you were not disciplined when all this happened.
They came when you were out of discipline.
Nothing good happens without discipline.
You talk of sickness, you talk of this, you talk of that.
Any time you are disciplined, what follows? Good.
Any time you are not disciplined, what follows? Bad.
Nothing good happens without discipline.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Happy Easter!
Tell your neighbour, "Nothing good happens without discipline".
Becoming rich and influential without the right character is all type.
It is out of balance.
Jesus does not want us to succeed financially and lose our kids, children to drugs
and lose our children to militants and lose our children to the world.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Pick that word and take it home before you begin to celebrate. Go and put your home in order.
Sometimes you say, "I run after business... Look at my friend".
You want to be a Christian? Look at your children. What are you doing with them?
You want to be great and abandon them to drugs. You want to be great and allow them to be in the world.
You can never be great in the Lord.
All the way to Calvary He went for me
He went to set me free
Becoming rich and influential without the right character is all type.
It is out of balance.
The children, they are part of your blessing.
If one is faulty, all are faulty. If one is bad, all are bad.
There is no shortcut.
Life is a marathon, not a sprint - no shortcuts.
We want to use a shortcut.
You see the world today.
When you see many general managers, these are the people who cannot manage their homes.
Many heads of parastatals cannot manage their homes.
Many want to own their own company, and they cannot keep their own car clean.
What kind of company do you expect from people like that?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Many want to get married because of their age but they cannot keep their pet at home.
They cannot manage their pet at home but they want to get married because of their age.
This is what turns the whole world upside down today.
You that cannot keep your car clean, you want to own your own company.
You cannot manage your home but you are the head of big, different companies.
MD of the companies.
What can you expect from such a company?
Charity begins at home.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Happy Easter!
Jesus was able to manage His team.
That is why He paid the supreme price wee are here today to celebrate.
Jesus does not want any one of us to end our days saying,
"I should have been, I would have been, I could have been".
Happy Easter!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbour, "Jesús does not want us to end our days saying,
'I could have been, I should have been, I would have been'".
Happy Easter!
The SCOAN Sunday Service.
We are here today.
Your kid is at home; your children are at home.
You can't say, "Let us go!" They will tell you, "What are you celebrating?"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
But you are the leader, controller, instructor, commander of other children.
We want to use shortcuts.
Life is a marathon.
You want to be God's person - follow His process.
Overflow Congregation
Nothing good happens without discipline.
Nothing good happens without what?
Discipline!
This is whyJesus is trying to build character now so that when you get to the place of your destiny,
you will not crash, explode and lose it all.
Many lose it all today. You see the world - going up and losing it all.
Greatness - lose it all. Popularity, fame - lose it all because we are not following the process.
Tell your neighbour, "I know why I'm going through what I'm going through.
God is busy building character".
Yes, that character will help you.
When you are at the place of your destiny, it will help you to sustain, to stand the challenges of time.
You say, "Ah! My business is not going well! Why is my business like this?
Why do I not have a job? What's wrong?
I'm sick. I am a Christian".
Ask God for the reason.
It may be that God is busy building character.
Say after me, "God is trying to build character NOW!".
I can´t hear you.
God is trying to build character NOW!
That NOW should be in a capital form - Capital N, Capital O, Capital W.
If you don't get that character NOW, whatever you achieve, you will likely lose it!
Character is a tonic.
There's nothing you can keep for a while, for long, without character.
Character is the oil in the lamp.
Whatever you achieve is that flame. The light that is burning; but the oil in the lamp is character.
And if there is no oil in the lamp, what will happen to the lamp?
It will be off!
One thing off!
One, one, one, one!
Influence will be off!
The glory will be off!
Popularity will be off! They say, "Where is this man? They can't hear of him again!"
The oil is dry - that is character.
Are you with me?
The oil in the lamp is character.
The lamp light is what?
Proceeds.
Proceeds could be money, fame, popularity, this, that, president, minister, senate.
These are proceeds, but the oil inside the lamp is character.
And when the oil dries, all the proceeds will soon...
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If I were you, just put a lamp on your altar.
I know you have everything you need.
Electricity is there but electricity apart, put a lamp on your table.
It is a symbol that the light there is proceeds.
The oil inside the lamp is character.
Any time you fail to put oil and you try, you see the light off.
That is your life. When you put a lamp on your altar, it's a symbol of you. You are that lamp.
If you look at my altar, you see a lamp there. There is electricity. People say, "Why that lamp?"
Yes, it is a symbol.
When the oil is gradually drying, you see a kind of dim light.
That is, you are not able to identify anything with that dim light.
This is the life of many of us today.
Your proceeds are not enough. It's causing you trouble.
Where you are supposed to give 1 million naira, 1 million dollar, you are given 5000 naira.
What is not done well, is not done at all.
They have given you a name.
You don't know what to do again because what you have is no longer enough because the oil is drying.
We are talking of dividends of Easter
What is Easter?
He went for you to make you fit, to make you qualified,
to make you a friend of God, to make you dine and wine with God.
You can still reinstate your way and put things right.
Those of you that know that you cannot even manage the little home you have
but you are the head of companies,
you can still look back because you'll soon lose it all.
You have money, influence and you have lost your kid, your children to drugs,
militants, the world - you can still look back.
It is not too late to carry them along.
What is right is right; what is not right is not right.
Nothing good happens without discipline.
We look at all our weaknesses, faults and say,
"It is not going to happen to me - what happened to others".
What happens in the name of God is not about your weakness, pitfalls, faults;
It is about what Jesus achieved, did for us.
He made you qualified.
I say, it can happen to you, in the name of Jesus!
If satan wants to rob you of your blessings, he will say to you,
"Because of your weakness!"
He will immediately remind you of your weakness, your faults.
And when that begins to come into your heart, you know it is the work of satan.
You know you came from home.
Many of you through flight - you know it's fire of life to fly on the air.
Human being pilots - he may be a drunkard, smoker.
But that is fire of life.
If God has not prepared you in advance, you will not be able to skip through.
The SCOAN Sunday service
Say, "He prepared me in advance before putting me inside the aircraft, train, vehicle to here".
Overflow Congregation
If God had not prepared you, it would have been very easy for your enemy to get you.
The SCOAN Sunday service
From one flight to stopover, sleeping, joining another flight,
back, entering a car - oh my God!
He had prepared you in advance before putting you...
Say, "He had prepared me in advance before putting me in the fire of life".
You can say to your neighbour, "Happy Easter!"
Jesus of Nazareth must built character
so that when you get to the place of your destiny, you will not crash.
Now, here is character.
Happy Easter!
Answer me.
You know I told you that the Word becomes part of us by meditation.
The Word of God becomes part of you by what? - Meditation.
See.
Sometimes when I'm alone, I continue to fire on.
I told you I watched a game yesterday - football.
I have time; it´s not a sin. I was just sitting there and watching while this one was in my hand.
I saw that number 7.
"Jesus, Jesus, Jesus!" - I said, "Which Jesus are they calling?"
He was about to score. They said, "Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, go, go!"
I said, "Ah! This one is not Jesus; he cannot score".
The SCOAN Sunday service
Hallelujah!
Can I hear your lesson and the message you are taking home this Easter?
Come on. Someone there.
Tell me about your children now.
Jesus does not want you to succeed and lose your kid to drugs.
Jesus does not want me to succeed and lose my kids, so thereby I must work on my character
and my children - I must work on their spiritual life.
You can see that I´m drawing very close to you because I like what you are saying.
Yes, daddy.
Jesus does not want you to succeed and lose your kid to drugs.
He does not want you to succeed financially and lose your kid to militants.
He does not want you to succeed and lose your kid to the world.
What do you want to say about that?
Yes, daddy.
The one at home.
By the grace of God, I'm teaching them the way of God because I want them to grow in the fear...
And they listen to you?
Yes, daddy. By the grace of God, they listen to me.
Your daughter listens to you?
Yes, daddy, by the grace of God.
Don´t - why the grace of God? It is the grace of God.
Nowadays when you hear a Christian saying, "By the grace of God, I will get there", it is a lie.
He is saying, expressing a doubt.
When a man says, "By the grace of God, I will get there", he is expressing doubt.
What kind of grace?
Grace is not a mango.
Okay, we are helping you. Now you know the message, you are to go back.
You have a job to do.
Most especially that daughter. You have to go back and work on her.
Yes, daddy.
Okay?
If not, you may likely lose it all.
That is, the blessing you have.
Yes, daddy.
The SCOAN Sunday service
Thank you.
When I heard the message, "Jesus does not want me to succeed because He wants to prepare me
or prepare my children for my future",
this made me to remember a dream I had some time ago.
Before you go further - did you listen to the way she turned it now?
She said it is like God is building character, that is why her success is delayed.
If you don't have character and you succeed, you may likely lose it all.
Clap for her.
So, for you now to be thinking that "God does not answer my prayer"...
No, who told you that God does not answer your prayer. He loves you; He´s busy building character.
Nothing good happens without discipline.
I think the message I will take home is that
nothing good happens without discipline.
All challenges a human being has is a part of discipline.
You cannot have salvation without discipline.
Clap for him.
Did you listen to that?
It's not possible to have salvation without discipline.
If you have that salvation, you will lose it all.
No salvation without discipline. Nothing good happens without discipline.
Thank you, sir. Thank you very much.
Without salvation - you're looking for salvation, trying to earn it.
Because everything you earn,
it's only by the time you agree with yourself that "This is what I can do,
that money is good" - but not just getting money from all angles,
there is money that is without process
and when it comes to you, it's actually not going to help you.
That money is good but with process.
Thank you. Clap for him.
Did you listen to that?
So it is time now to begin to think inwardly.
Many of us here are heading a company.
Many of us here own their own company.
There are many MDs, general managers here.
You can still look back. Even your little house, you cannot manage them.
Are you talking of those of us that have a company -
your car, house - one can see that this is a general manager.
There are many marriages today - tension, so much tension
because God's time is the best.
Take a lesson.
We also have many here that are blessed - you have money, you have enough.
Where are your children?
Many of our children - we have lost them to the world.
If you don't quickly run to God and look back,
seek for solution for these children, you may likely lose it all.
Like I have said, Jesus does not want us to end our days saying,
"I could have been, I should have been, I would have been".
Let´s hear from you.
I have learnt that before you believe, you must get your own revelation.
You must believe in God through the Holy Spirit to get a revelation.
There's nothing that you can become - an MD - without carrying your children along.
You must always carry your children along.
Did you listen to that?
They are an integral part of you.
On the last day, our Lord Jesus will ask you, "Where are they?"
Will you tell Jesus, "I have lost them to drugs"?
Will you tell Jesús, "I have lost them to militants"?
Will you tell Jesus, "I have lost them to the world"?
Question mark.
The SCOAN Sunday service
Thank you.
Anyone?
Okay, my brother here.
I've learned that life is a marathon, not a sprint
and God can use any situation to discipline us.
So we must value the process.
Thank you. Clap for him.
Did you listen to that?
Our brother is taking us through to process.
That if you want to become God's person, you must follow His process.
Are you there?
Let's hear from our sister.
Good morning, Church.
Good morning.
What I learnt today is that there is no shortcut in life.
That as we are a work of art in God's hand, we must wait patiently
and follow His process so that whatsoever we will receive in life,
will stand a test of time. Emmanuel!
Did you listen to that?
She said, you are a work of art.
Thank you.
You know you take a pen, you are taking a picture, trying to draw some objects.
Tell your neighbour, "I'm a work of art".
Again and again.
If you want to be a person of God, you must follow His process.
Thank you.
What I'm taking back home with me - I have learnt here that
we cannot separate Christianity from power.
The revelation I got here for myself is that
the wisdom is to see but seeing is also power from God and responsibility
which means, through the power of God, we can change the situation.
My brother must like power.
Power - my brother likes power. Clap for my brother.
You can see in the statement that he mentioned power up to four times.
That is, revelation brings conviction and conviction brings real movement.
Real movement - power steps.
Can you understand that?
Power steps - steps with intent and purpose.
Clap for my brother. Thank you very much.
With this, you can know if you are born again.
You can know.
The question - what kind of Christian do you want to be?
Ask you neighbour.
What kind of Christian do you want to be?
I can't hear you.
Because there are many Christians - Christians without the power of the Holy Ghost,
Christians with the power of the Holy Ghost.
Because to be a Christian, you must be led by the Holy Ghost.
And many Christians today are not led by the Holy Ghost.
That's why I'm asking you what kind of Christian you want to be.
What kind of leader do you want to be? - A leader with purpose.
A leader with difference
So when we talk of power, as a Christian, you need to ask what kind of Christian you want to be.
When the Bible says in 1 Corinthians verses 12-30,
"No one can say 'Jesus is Lord' without the help of the Holy Ghost",
no one can be a Christian without the help of the Holy Ghost.
Thank you. Our brother.
Good morning, Church.
The lesson I learnt today, that I will take home is about character and self-discipline.
We are not to rush to have big things while we cannot manage small things.
The man of God talked about not being able to clean a small car,
but you want to run a fleet of Benz.
Clap for my brother.
Did you listen to that?
Yes! You want to have your own company,
fleet of companies and you cannot keep your car clean.
You'll be very surprised to see many owners of companies if you open their garage.
They cannot do anything. They have housemaid, houseboy - money cannot do anything.
What are you talking about?
You have to lead by example; if not, you will lose it all.
Like that.
We have many of us here that this message is talking to.
You own companies.
Not one, not two, not three companies.
In a week, you may not even go to any of these companies
because you have money to employ people to do the job for you.
For how long will you continue this?
Can money run a company?
Your presence is a good thing to your worker and to your follower.
They want to know how you became what you are.
They want to know how you talk.
They want to know how you move. They want to know how you relate with people.
That will give them hope for the future.
But hardly - your staff, workers hardly see you one day.
They don't know their boss.
You live in Heaven.
Let's hear from our brother.
The word that I'm carrying with me home
is that the Word of God becomes part of us through meditation.
Yes.
The more you meditate, the more you hear the voice of the Lord
and the more you become the person of the Lord and will follow His processes.
Clap for him.
Did you listen to that?
Meditation brings revelation; revelation brings conviction
and conviction brings real movement.
Can you see? - Process.
If you want to be God's person, you must follow His process.
Meditation. What am I talking about now? Begin to meditate.
Meditate, meditate, meditate, meditate.
And turn it over and over in your heart.
Revelation comes and that revelation will become conviction and lead you to real movement.
The SCOAN Sunday service
Yes, the message I'm taking home is that life is a marathon and not a sprint.
and that discipline plays an important role in our lives.
Can you tell me how this affects you?
Me..?
Because you are a young man..
Yes, sir.
I know you are talking by your experience.
He's laughing.
People want to learn..
We are hungering for the knowledge, this Easter.
Hungry for the knowledge.
Most of us want to be successful so fast by using the shortcut.
Thank you. Clap for him.
Did you listen to that?
He's a young one so I know. He said, we want to make a shortcut,
forgetting that life is a marathon, not just a sprint.
Shortcut means, we are not waiting for God to build character.
If you don't wait for God to build this character in you,
by the time you get to your place of destiny, what happens?
Something will crash, explode and you will likely lose all.
This is what is happening today.
This is what is happening all over the world.
Character - like I have said - is oil in the lamp.
When there's no oil in the lamp, what happens to the light?
That's just it! That's just you!
Now with this message, now you know why you are going through what you are going through.
It is never proper to base faith on our improvement after prayer.
Tell your neighbour,
"It is never proper to base faith on our improvement after prayer".
Again..
"It is never proper to base faith on our improvement after prayer."
"God, I need, I need, I need a car. I need a car. I need to pay my debt."
But after the prayer, nothing. The prayer seems not to answer.
I now say I have no faith. - No!
God is busy building character.
God knows, "If I give you what you want immediately - Ha!
Something will crash and you will likely lose it all".
So you say,"I have no faith". That is why you have stopped going to church.
"I have no faith." That is why you refuse to pray.
You pray, "Lord, I want to pass my examination".
But when the result come out, you find that there's some setback or failure.
You now say, "I fast. I pray. Even my friend that was not fasting, that was not praying,
has first class. But I fast, I pray but see me. I have third class".
No, the reason why you will not have your result is: God is holding you a little back;
He wants to build your character.
When the character comes, you can stand for the greatness that is coming.
The SCOAN Sunday service
The result of your prayer now is not all that important now but more important tomorrow.
Tell your neighbour again.
The result of my prayer now is not all that important now but more important tomorrow.
That is, what you are going to receive today after prayer from God
is important but more important tomorrow.
You need it in a difficult time; in the trial time, you need those results.
So please, God is trying to build character.
Listen to that. God is trying to do what? - To build character.
So that when you get to the place of your destiny,
you will not crash, explode and lose it all.
Okay, next.
I just want to thank God for revealing this revelation to me.
Because what I was going through, I didn't know that God was disciplining me.
My life was in a mess and I just thought, "What is going on in my life?"
Because my first time of coming here to this church, it was not for the salvation of my soul.
It was all about - I wanted business, making money.
But myself, I didn't have the character. Even the way I used to talk to people,
it was not representing that I am a Christian.
So I just want to thank God for this revelation
that God is building my character and it is God's processing.
Clap for my mum.
Good!
Did you listen to that?
My mum now realised that nothing good happens without discipline.
And what gives us discipline? - God's character.
It is God's character that brings discipline; the proceeds of God's character is discipline.
Nothing good happens without what?
Without discipline.
Salvation cannot come without discipline.
Even the blessings we are waiting for or the healing we are waiting for now -
if you are healed without discipline, you will likely lose it.
If you are blessed without discipline, you will likely lose it.
If you are blessed without discipline, it will crash. And it will crash at a time you will need it most.
Emmanuel! What I've learnt today is that yes, God has provided for all our needs
but we are the cause of the delay
because we don't want to submit to God's discipline process.
Clap for my brother.
That is, we are the cause of delay because we don't want to submit.
We just want something from God but we are not ready to submit.
We are not ready for salvation; salvation is salvation.
We are not ready for salvation so we are the cause of delay.
Are you ready?
So listen to my brother. He said, "We are the cause of delay".
- Yes!
Hallelujah! Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday service